What?
His name here
shouldn't be "Park Real Son."
- He's not Park Village Head.
- Let's see the photo.
- Did he assume a new identity?
- Wait, this is our village's--
- Wait, what?
- No way!
- Wait, that's our village's--
- Wait, what?
PARK VILLAGE HEAD'S ID IS FAKE?
Who changes their identity like this?
- This is such a sloppy way to do it.
- Unbelievable.
- He's grabbing something!
- You just changed the photo!
- You'll anger the gods!
- Hang on.
Come on, man. That's not funny.
Fine, I'll let you live.
- Hurry up and explain this to us.
- He's scary.
- Seriously, what is this?
- I'm scared to go near him.
Why did you stick your photo
on Park Real Son's ID?
He must be dead.
No, I...
If I'm being honest,
when I came to this village,
I had to find ways to settle here.
I saw there was an old lady
who was living alone,
so I took care of her
as if she were my own mother.
I saw her family photo and found out
that her son and I look alike.
She even got us mixed up
and thought I was her real son,
so I figured I should act like I was him.
And then what?
- So what happened to Park--
- All right. I'll come clean.
- Okay.
- I...
I...
I have killed someone before.
- What the heck?
- I had no choice.
- When? Who? Park Real Son?
- Who? Park Real Son?
Park Real Son came back.
Of course,
that's typical for identity theft.
That's how it always goes.
- Always.
- But let me make this clear.
I didn't kill Jang Je-in.
Where did you hide Park Real Son's body?
Wait a minute.
- Jeez, you scared me. What is it?
- What is it?
Remember that emergency text
- about the landslide at 8:35 p.m.?
- The landslide.
- Let's check out the mountain.
- The mountain?
CAN PARK REAL SON'S BODY BE THERE?
Maybe... Let's go.
- No way!
- Hurry. Let's go!
Shouldn't we let him
finish his story first?
Do you have more to tell us?
Darn it.
- There's something here. It's a pit.
- What's with that rope?
- Maybe he hid it there.
- There's something here.
This is...
I said I didn't kill her!
I swear I didn't kill Jang Je-in!
- Are we going up or not? Make a decision.
- I'm terrified!
- Hurry. Let's dig before he gets here.
- Come on!
- Hurry.
- Hurry up!
- He's coming!
- Is there a shovel or something?
Okay, we get it. But you're scaring us,
so don't come up here.
I said I didn't kill Jang Je-in.
- We get it.
- Stay there.
- What about Park Real Son?
- Where is he?
- Park Real Son's murder alone is enough...
- He'll get arrested anyway.
I dumped him far away from here.
- Far away?
- Very far away.
Mr. Village Head has been suspicious
of outsiders from the start.
The killer must be one of the outsiders.
Of course,
Mr. Village Head is absolutely right!
He's always been hostile
toward outsiders in the village.
But it turns out
he was an outsider himself.
How did he end up in this village?
And who is he, really?
- Far away?
- Okay, since you've decided to come clean...
What kept you busy on the eve festival...
- What kept you busy on the eve festival...
- Who's that?
- Someone's here.
- What?
- The hotel manager is here.
- That's Chong Manager.
The manager must've seen something.
- Hey, Chong Manager.
- Hello, Mr. Manager.
Hey, Chong.
- Yes, hello.
- Hello.
The guest staying in Room 305
is Jang Je-in, right?
- Yes, that's correct.
- Right.
- What time did she leave yesterday?
- Well...
She took a cab around 10:20 p.m.
- Around 10:20 p.m.?
- She took a cab?
Around 10:20 p.m.?
That's right. I saw her.
Je-in tossed the ring I gave her
and then she took a cab at 10:20 p.m.
to her hospital.
You knew all that and didn't tell us?
Well, you never asked.
To the hospital?
She said she was meeting
someone important,
but who could be more important than me?
Just go lie over there.
Who was the important person
the victim was planning to meet?
Our top priority is finding out
why Jang Je-in returned to this village
after five years.
Did anyone else come by the hotel
who wasn't a guest?
- Mr. Village Head was here.
- Village Head?
- Well...
- When?
He was here
throughout the entire eve festival,
but he did step out twice.
Around 9:20 p.m.,
during the shamanic rite,
- he and the governor of Lunacy District
- Oh, him.
- went into our conference room.
- And?
Oh, and he was there
during the singing contest,
but around 10 p.m.,
he suddenly slipped away.
He looked like he was in a hurry.
Around 10 p.m.?
What could've kept him so busy
that he couldn't focus on the event?
WHERE DID YOU GO?
This guy's got a secret for sure.
We have to dig deeper into him.
MEANWHILE, PARK VILLAGE HEAD
IS DIGGING DEEPER INTO PARK SHAMAN
What happened to Shaman's younger brother?
She said he went missing,
but she gathered his things
and set them up
like she was mourning for the deceased.
His case is being overlooked,
so I'm going to dig into it.
What's this?
Over here!
Gosh, give me a break.
What is it?
Come here, hurry.
Who dared disturb my shrine?
The spirits' fury will be upon you!
My goodness.
- Let's lift it up.
- One, two, three.
Oh shit.
What?
What were you thinking?
What's going on?
One, two, three.
Oh shit.
- What?
- What were you thinking?
THERE'S A DEAD BODY
INSIDE THE STATUE OF BUDDHA?
Never seen a mummy before?
MEMORIAL TABLET OF THE DEAD, BROTHER
You may find it shocking
if you don't know much about shamanism.
This is a mummy, that's all.
-"Memorial tablet of the dead, Brother."
- That's right.
So that's your brother?
- You said he's missing.
- It must be him.
-"Memorial tablet of the dead, Brother."
- Well...
Fine, you got me.
That's my younger brother.
But you said he went missing.
I did say that, and he did go missing.
- I never said he was still alive.
- But...
Hey, Handsome!
We found her brother's corpse.
- What?
- We found her brother's corpse.
You found a corpse?
- This is her brother?
- Hey, show some respect for the deceased.
- Man, this is...
- Everyone, please take a step back.
Good heavens!
My goodness.
- Jeez, that's scary.
- You murderer.
How could she have kept
his skeletonized body in there?
It was truly a shock to my eyes.
What's all this fluid?
Are they parts of his body
that decomposed or something?
TRACES OF FLUID FROM THE MUMMIFICATION
- Why didn't you say he was murdered?
- Explain all this to us.
- Where did you find him?
- Why'd you say he was missing?
After he went missing,
the police and I looked everywhere
but couldn't find him.
But while searching
in that mountain over there,
I finally found his body.
But the body was already
severely mutilated.
You can't hold a funeral
when the body is in such a state.
If you do, the soul is cursed
to wander the afterlife forever.
So I preserved the body
and attended to him
- while quietly looking into what happened.
- And that's currently ongoing?
How was the body mutilated?
- His organs were missing and whatnot.
- His organs?
- His organs were gone?
- Yeah.
When exactly did he go missing?
- Five years ago.
- In 2013?
Yeah.
You'll see in my ledger that I performed
a huge rite in front of the hospital.
That was worth 100 million won.
- It was for a patient there.
- Okay.
I persuaded them, saying they were
possessed by an evil spirit
and performed a huge rite for them.
Then, Je-in reported me to the police,
claiming I was stealing her patients
by performing rites near her hospital.
Right, she was taken into custody
and questioned for ten days.
Yeah, so I was in lockup,
and that's when my brother disappeared.
But the thing is, that's exactly
when Je-in disappeared too.
And the hospital
has been abandoned since then.
- Something big must've happened back then.
- Exactly.
So how could I not suspect her?
It makes sense that I thought,
"Did this bitch report me to the police
and do something to my brother
while I was gone?"
It's natural to think that, no?
They have history. Quite an intense one.
But if she's blaming Je-in
for her younger brother's death,
I think that could be
her motive for murder.
First things first, Park Shaman.
Can we see your phone?
- Of course, you can. Here.
- Great.
- Go ahead and look.
- Okay.
Why are you laughing?
- Hey, I knew it. Look at this here.
- What is it?
- Where did Chong Manager go? Get him back.
- Why?
She and Chong Manager are close friends.
- They must be dating.
- That's why...
He's my client.
The night before the murder,
"Chong, remember the pre-rite meeting
for the eve festival at eight tomorrow?"
"I'll get there 30 minutes early to do..."
On the day of the murder.
"Shaman, sorry for the late reply."
"Director Jang left around 10:20 p.m.
She said she was going to the hospital."
- That's all.
- Why was he reporting all this?
He was the one
who told me Je-in was in town.
So I asked him
to keep me updated about her.
- I wanted to see her and find out
- To go see her?
if she was responsible
for my brother's death.
But he only got back to me
at that late hour.
So you couldn't go see her?
- I was here at 10:20 p.m.
- You were here?
So your alibi still holds.
Sounds like all this mess began in 2013.
The hospital was shut down,
Jang Je-in left,
and Handsome kept coming back here
every July 31st for the past five years.
Shaman's younger brother
died that year too.
But then again,
there's another mystery
regarding An Doctor.
She became suspiciously wealthy
in those five years.
Just what happened to her?
She never elaborated on that,
to be honest.
As for this car...
AN DOCTOR'S IV POLE
Look here!
- What is it?
- Over here!
What is it?
Isn't this An Doctor's?
I don't know.
Look.
There's blood on this!
On the IV pole.
Where? Whose blood is it?
- Is it my Je-in's?
- How should we know?
- Where?
- Here.
- Detective, I have something to tell you.
- Yes?
I was quietly praying to the gods earlier.
I was praying to them to give me wisdom
to solve the case.
I was ready for possession
when it struck me.
I figured out what An Doctor
was doing for her VIP patients.
- How?
- What is it?
What was that patient's name?
Something Terminal?
- Na Terminal!
- Yes, Na Terminal.
They were a terminal patient
- who paid An Doctor 180 million.
- And?
My patients call me their savior.
"Savior"? How? What makes her a savior?
What kind of salvation
can she give terminal patients?
That's when it hit me.
Assisted dying.
- Really?
- She's euthanizing them.
She calls herself an orthopedist
but doesn't carry enough surgical tools
to treat her VIP patients.
But she does have syringes,
drugs, and an IV pole.
She's getting paid
to illegally euthanize them.
For those kind of patients,
money isn't the issue.
- Because their condition is critical.
- Exactly.
- They just want to find peace.
- Right, because of the pain.
Give me that bag for a minute.
Let's frisk her!
Don't you dare!
- Why, you little...
- Okay, I get it. Stop.
- Just give me your bag.
- Okay.
CELL PHONE HANDED OVER VOLUNTARILY
- What?
- Hang on.
I don't think that's her phone.
- Wait, then whose is it?
- Whose is it?
An Doctor's phone is here.
- An Doctor's phone is here.
- Right here.
- Isn't that Na Terminal's phone?
- Is it?
This must be the VIP's.
Look. An Doctor wrote,
"I'm running late due to the landslide."
- Then this is the VIP's.
- It must be.
- What?
- Look at this.
ON THE VIP'S CELL PHONE
"Euthanasia live stream"?
See? I told you she performed euthanasia.
You're an amazing shaman.
- It's not Na Terminal's, but the VIP's.
- Truly amazing.
- Here, look at this.
- What is it?
There's a video.
A LIVE VIDEO?
Hello.
This is Eat Well and Die Well.
The big day is finally here.
Enjoy the video,
and I hope all of you will succeed
in unaliving yourselves.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Any last words you'd like to say?
- This is An Doctor's voice.
- Yeah, it is.
You're really a doctor, right?
Of course, I am.
I'm Director Jang Je-in.
JANG JE-IN'S EMPLOYEE ID
- What?
- She's talking.
She impersonated her.
Wow, she was pretending to be Je-in.
It's not going to hurt, is it?
Of course not. This is the quick
and relaxing LOVE DIVE consultation.
-"LOVE DIVE"?
-"Quick and relaxing LOVE DIVE"?
- That sounds familiar.
- That website.
JOIN US WHEN DATING GETS TOUGH
Five, four, three, two, one.
Jeez, you're gonna croak anyway.
What's with all the bothersome questions?
- Oh my.
- Oh, that's terrifying.
Hold your breath and life die
And that's it
for today's exciting euthanasia!
Huh? What the?
- She said, "Huh? What the?"
- And that part got recorded.
- Everyone.
- What's up?
I discovered the truth behind LOVE DIVE.
- LOVE DIVE!
- What is it?
This looks like an online community
run by An Doctor.
Look, it says "Savior" here.
"Join us when dating gets tough."
It looks like a dating counseling space.
- That's a facade.
- That's how she set it up,
- but actually--
- Over here.
I found an option to switch modes.
Click it, and it turns into dark mode.
"Join us when dating gets tough.
Hold your breath and dive."
"Join us when living gets tough.
Hold your breath and life die."
- Oh, you're right.
- So in light mode, it's about dating.
But when you switch to dark mode,
it's about death consultations.
ANESTHETIC → NEUROMUSCULAR BLOCKING AGENT
→ TOXIC SUBSTANCE
THREE DRUGS ADMINISTERED IN ORDER,
QUICK AND PAINLESS DEATH GUARANTEED
DATING COUNSELING, REQUIRED HEARTS
TIME REQUIRED, LEVEL OF PAIN & COST
(♥ X 1 = 10 MILLION WON)
Where the heck
did you euthanize all of them?
Euthanasia?
We have all the proof right here.
"Hold your breath and dive."
I didn't euthanize them.
I saved them.
And where did you do that?
In my Je-in's hospital?
In the nurses' station
on the fourth floor.
- Nurses' station.
- Let's go.
Okay, first question.
Did you or did you not impersonate Je-in?
- I did.
- I knew it.
Did you ever get caught?
No, never.
As for the ID card,
I only took it when she threw it out
after shutting down the hospital.
But why did you pretend to be her?
Because this is an abandoned hospital,
and I'm not so well-known as a doctor,
some VIP patients have trouble
putting their faith in me.
So I show them this ID
to get them on board.
- You've done that for five years?
- Yes.
So when did you kill the VIP in the video?
If you consider the timing,
Je-in took a cab at 10:20 p.m.
and came here.
She could've crossed paths with An Doctor
while she was performing the procedure.
- What time did you do it?
- The director's office is right next door.
Something could've easily gone down.
Okay, let me tell you
what I haven't before.
- I did see Je-in here.
- What?
- I told you.
- When?
Around 10:27 p.m.
You mentioned the wheelchair earlier.
So you euthanize your clients,
load them onto a wheelchair,
and dump them in the lake.
That's right.
Then you came back?
- So you came from the lake.
- Normally, I don't.
Oh, so you came back to kill Je-in.
Listen.
I performed the procedure here,
moved the body with a wheelchair,
and then got to the parking lot
where you saw the wheelchair.
I got that far until Je-in came in
out of nowhere.
Right!
So I hid behind the wheelchair.
Then the fireworks started going off.
I took that chance to load the body
in my trunk and then went to the lake.
But because I was impersonating Je-in,
I got worried she might've found out
about my procedures.
So I had to come back to check
and see why Je-in had come back here.
What did you see when you came back?
She wasn't here, and then I was
immediately summoned as a suspect.
- No, I think she's lying right now.
- That can't be right.
Listen.
- At the end of that live video,
- Yeah?
the VIP was already dead, right?
But she went, "Huh? What the?"
Huh? What the?
I bet that's when she saw Je-in.
No, I only said that
because I had just found the camera.
I'd never seen a VIP client
who streamed their procedure.
There's no proof of that though.
How do we know it wasn't because of Je-in?
If she ran into Je-in
while performing euthanasia,
she could've impulsively murdered her.
Why did she have to come back
to the hospital from the lake?
If there's one thing we know,
it's that the culprit always returns
to the scene of the crime.
Maybe she came back
after dumping the VIP's body
to take care of Je-in's body
that was hanging on the wall.
Okay, everyone. Come with me.
Let's continue the conversation over here.
- What's the matter?
- Diesel!
This diesel container is identical
to the ones in the Yeonjidol Gas Station.
- You're right.
- It even says "Yeonjidol Gas Station."
This must've been used for something.
Look at this.
This is the fire hydrant box,
and this is the circuit breaker box.
CIRCUIT BREAKER BOX
Wait, hold on.
-"Fuel with diesel"!
- It's fueled with diesel.
"Press the power switch on C,
the control panel."
Shouldn't we turn on the power first?
Power.
Power up, go!
- The power...
- It's not working.
POWER WON'T TURN ON
It says we have to supply A
with sufficient diesel fuel.
A is the fuel tank. This is where
we're supposed to put in the fuel.
- We have to put in the diesel.
- We do?
Let's get some from over there!
Go get it, quick!
- Go get it, quick!
- But I'm the detective.
- The youngest should go. Go on.
GET A MOVE ON, HANDSOME
- Go fetch it.
- Okay, I'll be right on that!
It's too late for that.
That lazy punk.
- Sir, I'll fetch it.
- Don't worry about it.
I'm the youngest.
So there was diesel fuel right here.
- We just need one, right? Or two?
- I'll take two back just in case.
- Is it really going to work now?
- I bet it's going to work.
- That's incredible.
- Okay, let's go.
- Were you waiting for me, An Doctor?
- No, I wasn't!
I wasn't.
I swear I wasn't.
- Good, you brought it. Let's pour it in.
- Here we go.
FILLING THE FUEL TANK WITH DIESEL
- Is it real fuel?
- Yeah.
Will it actually work?
- For real?
- That's enough.
- Okay, now the power.
- Try it.
Press C. Okay.
WELL?
POWER ON
IT REALLY WORKS
- I just got chills!
- We got it back up!
- This is crazy!
- The elevator!
- Guys, the lights are on!
- The lights are on!
That's insane.
- See this?
- The elevator's working!
Let's head up.
It opens!
ELEVATOR DOORS OPEN
FLOOR DIRECTORY
MENTAL WELLNESS PROGRAM
- There may be some hidden clues here.
- Maybe it leads to a rooftop garden.
- Well, I--
- They added a working elevator here?
- I can't believe this.
- I actually prefer taking the stairs.
- Get in here.
- Get in, we're a team here.
We're all in the same boat.
We're on the fourth floor, right?
- Yeah, so press five.
- Five.
Wow, this thing actually goes up?
Oh gosh.
I have a bad feeling about this.
I wanted to check the roof,
which is probably the last place
the body was.
This is a must in Crime Scene.
To find out how the murder happened,
we have to go to the roof.
I'm dying to check it out.
We have to use those stairs
to get to the roof.
Oh gosh. Look at this.
The way up looks dangerous.
- I'm so scared.
- I'm scared of the roof.
There's nothing here.
Wait, let's take a close look here.
Where was Je-in's body earlier?
- And how was it hanging?
- Be careful, Mr. Village Head!
Be careful, Mr. Village Head!
Don't go near there, Mr. Village Head.
You need to be here
to throw someone off the roof.
- Please don't.
- No, I don't think she was thrown off.
Are you saying she climbed over
- and went down there?
- Maybe she fell off while running away.
First off, it's not clear how she died.
Did the fall happen on purpose
or was it an accident?
Did she fall while running away
from the murderer?
We didn't find any traces of the body
being moved all the way up to the roof.
It doesn't make sense
that there are no traces whatsoever.
How did the killer do it?
I can't figure it out.
How did they manage it?
- Je-in!
- What happened?
What now?
Jang Je-in!
Jeez, you scared me.
Seriously, this is driving me nuts.
SEARCHING ROOM 501
What's this?
MYSTERIOUS MACHINE FOUND
- What's this thing? Know what this is?
- What do you mean?
"Metal detector"?
Oh, I saw that earlier.
There's a metal detector and other stuff.
It looks like someone brought them here
to find something hidden in this building.
- Is that really a metal detector?
- It's a water leak detector.
I brought it to look for leaks
and left it here after I finished.
- This one too?
- Yeah.
MEANWHILE, PARK SHAMAN
SEARCHES THE DIRECTOR'S OFFICE
Hold on a second.
BIRD'S-EYE VIEW PHOTO OF THE HOSPITAL
Wait. This lot was a site for a house.
Goodness.
DURING THE INITIAL EXAMINATION
THE PHOTO SHE SAW IN JANG COUSIN'S HOUSE
Yeonjidol Hospital.
I compared the bird's-eye view photo
and the photo of Jang Cousin's house
and realized they were on the same lot.
So I opened up both frames,
and you won't believe what I found.
FRAMED PHOTO OF JANG COUSIN'S HOUSE
What's this?
"Ten gold toads, fifteen gold bars"?
Would you look at that.
WHAT'S BEHIND THE BIRD'S-EYE VIEW PHOTO
OF THE HOSPITAL?
IN THE FRAME OF THE BIRD'S-EYE VIEW PHOTO
OF THE HOSPITAL
"Building Permit."
Je-in received a permit
- to build a medical facility, right?
- Yeah.
But originally,
Je-in's house was on this land.
Now, look at the back.
- It's marked X.
- Yeah.
That mark is where the hospital is.
I think the gold bars are right here.
- Jang Cousin.
- Yeah?
This is where the gold bars are, isn't it?
That's why you wanted to
buy this land from Je-in, isn't it?
- Well, actually...
- This isn't just a hospital site, is it?
My father kept this photo frame with him
until the day he died,
but I had no idea of its significance.
Until one day, I found this note
about gold toads and gold bars here,
- so I figured he buried them here.
- And?
But then she built this hospital
on top of that exact spot.
- See? I told you.
- Exactly.
I thought if I bought this land
from her for 500 million won,
I'd be able to dig around for that gold.
So I decided to make an offer,
but then she died
before I could even do so.
- Was the offer made or was it turned down?
- I never made the offer.
I only asked to meet her
but never got the chance.
- Wait.
- Let's see.
- It might not be the hospital.
- I even completed the agreement form.
BUILDING PERMIT
But the building in this picture
looks a bit different.
Check this out. "Details of the design
are subject to change."
Look closely.
Hang on.
It's here.
- That's not it.
- No, wait. Look at this.
- The floor counts don't match.
- Here.
One, two, three, four, five...
It has six floors!
- This building...
- There's no sixth floor!
- This building must have a hidden space.
There's no sixth floor!
- I got chills.
- Wait.
There should be another floor here,
but they blocked it off.
They turned a six-story building
into a five-story one.
The elevator will surely
take us to the sixth floor.
- Above the fifth floor.
- Hold on.
Hold on, let's see here.
- The emergency button?
- I pushed everything, but it didn't work.
- Try pressing the emergency button.
- Try pressing the buttons together.
Maybe something's hidden here.
- What is it?
- What's up?
There must be a button.
Here it is! I found it.
- All the buttons are there?
- Yeah, when you slide it up.
HIDDEN UNDERNEATH THE EMERGENCY BUTTON
IS ANOTHER BUTTON
Sliding it up did it.
This was it!
- Hang on.
- Wow, I had no idea.
- Get Mr. Village Head here!
- Mr. Village Head!
Park Village Head is running away!
He's getting away!
- I'm scared.
- I really had no idea.
- Goodness, this is...
- Where are we?
- We're here.
- This must be it.
- Incredible.
- We're here.
- Very impressive.
- This is insane.
I'm sweating. I'm hot.
Anyone who's faint of heart,
stand behind me.
- So brilliant.
- I'm scared.
I bet there's something here.
They must've removed body parts
and done all sorts of shady business here.
The lights are on too. My gosh.
Okay, everybody, relax.
Jang Cousin, you lead the way.
The sixth floor.
- Sixth floor.
- There's a secret door!
- Unbelievable.
- Oh my goodness.
MEANWHILE, PARK VILLAGE HEAD
Shouldn't we bring
Mr. Village Head up here too?
Exactly.
SO THEY BROUGHT HIM
I guess this was the main event.
Wow.
Oh, you got here quickly.
Wow, this is incredible.
Man, this is crazy.
What the heck is this place?
- I'll take one for the team and open this.
- My goodness.
So you go in first.
All right!
- Dang it!
- For goodness' sake!
JANG JE-IN'S SECRET
HIDDEN ON THE SIXTH FLOOR
SECRET OPERATING ROOM
WHAT HAPPENED IN THIS PLACE?
THE BRAIN: CAN'T CONTROL IT? REMOVE IT!
OPENING SOON, FRONTAL LOBE ON BLADE
- What is all this?
- This is insane.
- What is this?
- Seriously.
This must be where she died.
Yeah, this must be the place.
But where's the exit?
- Just a second!
- How do you get out of here?
- What's that?
- She must've died right here!
Maybe she fell while running out of here.
- There's blood here!
- That makes sense.
- So she was running.
- And then she fell from there.
- There are bloodstains.
- She ran and fell.
Look! Maybe the killer
bashed her head in with this.
The final blow to the head.
SURGICAL HAMMER
This must be what bashed her skull in.
She was running away and got caught.
She didn't fall.
- You're right.
- My Je-in's head.
DID SHE DISCOVER SOMETHING ELSE?
- Yeah, that's more like it.
- Look at those!
Wait, this is exactly how I looked too.
The eyes.
PATIENT: KIM LABORER
SURGERY RESULTS: FAILED
PATIENT: CHOI INJURY
PATIENT: HAN SURVIVOR
SURGERY RESULTS: SUCCESS
There were people whose eyes
looked exactly like Handsome's did
in his selfie.
Wait, so what did she do?
- Experiments?
- I know what this is!
- What is it?
But it's illegal.
- Of course, that's why she did it here.
- So what is it?
It's called psychosurgery,
where you use surgical methods to treat
people with psychiatric disorders
to help stabilize them.
So she meant to
treat his disorder surgically too?
You flip the patient's eyelids
and shove a pick up there.
Into my eyes?
It's a surgery that cuts the nerves.
Okay, so if you see here,
she shocks the anesthetized patient
with electricity to check if they're down.
Next, she lifts the eyelid,
inserts the surgical pick
through the socket,
uses a hammer to drive it in,
and then twists the pick
to excise the neural pathways.
This is the reason Jang Je-in was fired
from Illyu University Hospital.
Incompatible values.
Director Jang Je-in
was a different kind of doctor.
Unlike the mainstream approach of treating
psychiatric patients with drugs,
she held the radical belief
that frontal lobotomy was the answer,
which is what got her fired
from Illyu University Hospital in the end.
But someone like Je-in
would never give up.
That must be why
she came back to the rural Yeonjidol
and opened a psychiatric hospital.
She even created an operating room
on the sixth floor for herself
and continued her research in secret,
while believing
she was an exceptional doctor.
Look.
All the surgeries failed
except for Han Survivor's.
Remember the press conference
she was planning to hold?
Do you think it was related to this?
Park Village Head,
did you put her up to this?
Were you in on this?
No, listen to me, everyone.
- Wait!
- Give me a second!
As for Han Survivor...
I killed him.
- What?
- Well, that came out of nowhere.
- You said you only killed one person.
- You said you killed Park Real Son.
- You said you killed one person, not two.
- Just a minute!
The important thing right now
is who killed Jang Je-in.
Then when did you kill Han Survivor?
In 2013.
- In 2013?
- So that's it.
So does that mean Village Head
killed the only patient
that Je-in operated on successfully?
- Why did you kill him?
- Yeah, why?
Are you sure it was Han Survivor?
Not Choi Injury or Kim Laborer?
- Are you sure?
- We can confirm it with this.
IN THE DESK DRAWER
-"Transaction log."
- Is Han Survivor on it?
See? "Homeless person."
"Sent to Village Head."
"Village Head began procurement."
Only the numbers of people
sent or received were updated.
All entries mentioned Village Head's name,
page after page,
throughout all these years.
PARK VILLAGE HEAD PROCURED
THE HOMELESS FOR JANG JE-IN
She sent them over to Village Head
after they had the surgery.
That must've driven
the village's economic growth.
No wonder your business was successful.
You had plenty of unpaid labor!
Did you use them as beekeeping slaves?
Yes, she and I made a deal.
So you and Je-in were basically
in the human trafficking business.
Okay, let's think about this.
Je-in died right here, tonight.
And there's blood here on the hammer.
- The one you're holding, yeah.
- That matches her head wound.
- The size of the wound matches it.
- Yes, that's that.
But her chest wound
is from something else. It's wide.
This right here will explain that wound.
There's an electric saw here.
- Electric saw?
- Yeah.
- So the killer...
- That electric saw
was what slashed her wrist.
- Oh, her wrist.
- Right?
The way I see it,
the killer knew Je-in would come in here.
So they hid here, waiting for her.
They struck her head as she came in,
so she fell over here.
That's why the blood
is splattered all over here.
She collapsed,
but the killer turned her over
and attacked her chest.
But she wasn't dead yet,
so the extreme pain woke her up,
which led to a struggle.
Signs of a major scuffle are obvious.
They practically destroyed everything.
One of them ran while the other chased.
Hey, let's take a look here.
RECREATING THE CHAIN OF EVENTS
OUT THE WINDOW
From there?
- Let's say the killer stabbed her here.
- She got attacked,
- so she escaped this way.
- Right.
- The killer followed.
- And then...
She hung from there with this.
- Hey, I see bloodstains there.
- Exactly, wow.
Bloodstains and a bloody handprint.
- The killer closed in.
- She held onto this.
And then she fell from here.
- She couldn't have fallen from the roof.
- You're right.
Right?
She tried to grab onto the wires
or something and ended up there.
I doubt she did it on purpose.
Yeah, she probably got attacked here.
This is the exact spot.
I think she was cornered
after escaping through the window.
Seeing her hold onto the sign
with her left hand,
the killer must've hacked at her wrist.
I believe she fell after that,
got caught on the wires,
and died of severe blood loss.
What the...
What's that?
Who wore this, then?
Wait a minute.
- This blood is...
- What's this?
- The killer must've worn that.
- Exactly.
Could the killer have been someone
capable of performing a medical procedure
alongside the victim?
IS THE CULPRIT A MEDICAL PROFESSIONAL?
- Search everything.
- Wait!
What now?
- Search everything.
- Wait!
What now? What is it?
- This has braille on it!
- Braille!
A BRAILLE NECKLACE
- Braille?
- Your brother!
He must've been here!
My brother was here?
Oh gosh!
- So your brother...
- So she killed him in here?
We don't know if he was killed,
but this necklace was on the floor.
- We were expecting this though.
- Five years ago...
That's true.
But my brother has nothing to do
with those experiments.
- Did she kill him because it failed?
- Maybe she was going for his organs.
WERE ORGANS HARVESTED HERE TOO?
Okay, think about it.
The real question is,
who knew about this room?
- Of course.
- So who knew about it?
Not only did they know about the room,
but they also knew Je-in was coming here.
- The person who...
- They knew all about the experiments.
Okay, I wasn't aware of the surgeries.
But he's been here before.
- Chong Manager sent you that text tonight.
- That's right.
- You didn't know about Je-in coming.
- No.
But she was here
and saw Je-in entering the hospital.
Not on this floor.
I saw her at the entrance.
So An Doctor, you didn't know
about this room, right?
- I didn't.
- Same here, then.
- Did you know?
- Of course not.
- Are you sure?
- I really had no idea.
But you knew about the X mark
and the note about the gold.
- But that's buried.
- That clue led us here.
I just have one more question.
Why is there blood over there?
I mean in the freezer.
IN THE MEDICAL FREEZER
There are exploded blood bags.
OLD BLOODSTAINS?
What do you think was in here? Organs?
Let's head back downstairs.
Let's go and piece everything together.
Come on, let's go.
We found so many things
in that secret operating room
on the sixth floor.
And now we're confused.
My head's about to explode.
WHAT A HEADACHE...
What?
PARK VILLAGE HEAD'S WOODEN BENCH
LOOKS STRANGE
- What's wrong?
- Wait.
- Does it lift up too?
- What is it?
Is this bench supposed to come apart?
- No.
- Wait a minute.
- Ease up a bit, man.
- There's something in here!
- Is this bench supposed to open up?
- Wait.
- What is it?
- Hang on.
- Come on.
- What is it?
- Wait a minute.
- Why is this part lifting?
- No, it's not like that!
Hurry up.
What's that?
- What's that in the bench?
- Oh, from his past.
It looks like a photo of his gang.
Jeez, there's so much to uncover.
NEWSPAPER CLIPPINGS
What's this? Come over here.
My goodness.
"Demons Disguised as Humans."
"Bizarre murder spree
targeting the wealthy."
"Dualipa Gang arrested."
-"Dualipa"?
Sounds very Hollywood, doesn't it?
The Dualipa Gang.
Hey, but this wasn't just any old gang.
- It was a gang of brutal murderers.
- Right.
"Converted a farmhouse in a remote area
into a murder house."
"Young female VIP customers."
So they targeted the rich.
"But Park Enforcer, the gang's enforcer
and the only member
who isn't in custody yet,
has been on the run for six months."
So his name isn't Park Real Son
or Park Village Head.
It's Park Enforcer, as in a gang enforcer.
Right?
DUALIPA GANG'S ENFORCER
PARK ENFORCER
That's enough.
Mr. Park Enforcer.
He told you to stop!
So this is why he stole
Park Real Son's identity.
So Park Village Head...
I mean, Park Enforcer
was a member of the Dualipa Gang
that went on murder sprees.
He snuck into Yeonjidol Village,
killed Park Real Son,
assumed his identity, and has been
living as Park Village Head ever since.
That's horrifying.
"A, the sole victim of the Dualipa Gang
to have escaped,
came face-to-face with Park Enforcer."
"He is currently suffering from aphasia
due to extreme shock and trauma."
That's Han Survivor.
Survivor was the one who lived?
- He escaped from there.
- Oh, Han Survivor...
- So--
- So you met Han Survivor again here?
Yeah.
He knew about your past, then.
- Is that why you killed him?
- Yeah.
The only person
Je-in successfully operated on
happens to be connected to
Park Village Head.
He also knew Je-in
was planning to hold a press conference.
Jang Je-in, Han Survivor,
and the press conference.
The key to solving this case
could be the connection
between these three keywords
and Park Village Head.
Okay.
We found out that the building
was different from the original design,
and that led us to the secret room.
Now, what we need to focus on is this.
Who knew about that secret room?
At the moment,
everyone has denied any knowledge of it.
No one knew about it.
One more thing.
The fuel container.
The sixth floor can only be accessed
by powering the elevator with diesel.
That means the killer had to get the fuel.
So we need to find proof of purchase.
An Doctor was the only person
who had access to fuel.
You know what?
- I thought long and hard about this.
- Okay.
First of all, the killer has to be someone
who knows about that sixth-floor space.
Considering how An Doctor
actually worked in that hospital,
you might think that she's the person
who knew about that place.
Look at this.
We watched it earlier,
but I watched it again closely.
You're really a doctor, right?
- Of course, I am.
- Okay, stop.
Right here.
Do you see it?
This is what she was wearing!
It's this.
BLOODSTAINED SURGICAL GOWN
In the video,
she was wearing the same surgical cap
and mask found in the room.
And the sleeves in the video
- looked just like this too. It's a match.
- Was it visible on screen?
An Doctor was wearing this very gown!
- But even if I was,
- An Doctor
- all surgery gowns look the same.
- was wearing this.
This isn't different from others.
But there was no gown
in the nurses' station.
As I said,
An Doctor was wearing this very gown.
I always follow a particular routine.
I go to the nurses' station
on the fourth floor
and put on all the surgical gear
including a gown and a mask.
After the procedure,
I dump them into the lake with the body.
When did you start
performing these procedures?
After Je-in closed up her hospital.
So you've been the one using the building
ever since it shut down?
That's right.
Here's what I think.
During the past five years
after the hospital was shut down,
she used that operating room
on the sixth floor
to perform euthanasia,
following that routine of hers.
And that's it
for today's exciting euthanasia!
DURING THE PROCEDURE
But then
someone suddenly appeared, uninvited.
Huh? What the?
Namely, Jang Je-in.
Perhaps Je-in found out about everything,
including An Doctor impersonating her.
Let's say we all start off
in the same place.
There's no proof that any of us
knew about that room, right?
But I'm still a bit
suspicious of Park Village Head.
I wouldn't have suspected him
if it was just a run-of-the-mill gang.
But he's committed brutal murders before.
I don't think anyone without experience
can take another's life so easily.
And he took laborers from Je-in,
so there's no way
he didn't know about her experiments.
She had to have
done them somewhere, right?
Even if he didn't know
about the sixth floor,
he must've suspected
that there was a secret space.
I didn't know about the experiments
or the organ harvesting.
- I only--
- But you secured homeless people for her.
All I did was accept laborers from her.
Then how about this?
Let's say Je-in somehow managed
to find out who he really was.
She learned about his involvement
in that gang and whatnot,
and she tried to strike
some sort of a deal,
using that information as leverage.
- Then--
- No.
If she had tried that,
I would've killed her.
And you did kill her.
Me?
- Okay, then.
- Yes?
It seems the suspicions we shared
are pretty close to our final decision.
Now, we all have to look for evidence
to support those claims.
- Right?
- The fuel.
I need to look at the fuel.
Come here, look.
- This is the euthanasia video.
- Right.
But... Oh jeez.
- What's that?
- What's going on?
EMERGENCY TEXT
- What's that?
- What's going on?
LANDSLIDE OCCURRED ON YEONJIDOL MOUNTAIN,
LUNACY DISTRICT
- What's that?
- What's going on?
- It's a landslide, isn't it?
- Is it a landslide?
What's happening?
- Is it an earthquake?
What's going on?
It's an emergency. A natural disaster.
WARNING
LANDSLIDE PRONE AREA
- What the heck?
- What's happening?
What...
What a tiny landslide.
- So landslides do actually happen here.
- Hang on.
Let's go. We might find something.
Why did this landslide happen?
This area is prone to landslides.
They say this place
is prone to landslides.
Then perhaps there's something
buried in that mountain.
- We might find something.
- Oh gosh.
Is there a shovel or something?
OFF TO FETCH A SHOVEL
I knew I'd find a shovel here.
FOUND SHOVELS IN PARK VILLAGE HEAD'S HOME
Move. Let me start digging.
There's something off about this rock.
- Lift it up.
A SUSPICIOUS-LOOKING ROCK?
SUPERHUMAN STRENGTH
- You're strong.
- Cousin.
I guess that Viagura you took works.
Yeah, it sure is effective.
- Oh goodness.
- Hey, hold on.
- There's something there.
- Here it comes.
It's a shovel.
- A shovel?
- Yeah.
Someone buried--
- It's a knife!
- A knife!
- A shovel and a knife!
- It's a knife!
My goodness.
This looks like a sashimi knife,
doesn't it?
I guess this is the spot.
There's some kind of a mark here
in the shape of a cross.
- What's that?
- What is this?
- It's a skull.
It's a skull!
- Let's do a cleansing rite here too.
- Oh dear.
Where's the rest of the body?
- The rest is below it.
- Oh my gosh.
- Oh my.
- There it is.
What's this person wearing?
- Hospital gown?
- Looks like it.
- It's a hospital gown. Oh dear.
- Hospital gown?
"Yeonjidol Psychiatric Hospital."
This must be Han Survivor.
He's wearing the clothes
from the hospital.
- Han Survivor.
- Oh man.
- But why are his clothes...
- Why is it cut at the chest?
Why is there a hole in the chest?
- The chest area is torn apart.
- Hang on.
- There's a tear in the shape of a cross.
- Why is that?
Were his organs removed too?
Well...
It's a Dualipa Gang thing.
We always drew a cross
that symbolized fairness.
- Oh, was the gang's symbol a cross?
- We always marked the bodies with a cross.
Same length, both top and bottom.
So did you do this to mark him
as a victim of the Dualipa Gang?
I was worried that he might recognize me.
Of course, he didn't, but then...
- So his organs weren't harvested?
- What a heinous gang.
- No, it's just a mark on his flesh.
- What a scary bunch.
- If you mark the flesh...
- We get it.
Once the flesh is gone,
only the bones remain.
- We get it.
- Right?
- Then, those bones--
- Sure, but I'm standing at a cliff here.
We get it.
Okay, I'll climb down myself
before I'm pushed off the cliff.
- He buried one, why not another?
- Exactly.
- Go down.
- I should get out of here.
Why mark the chest of all places?
The wound on Je-in's chest
wasn't exactly a cross,
but maybe he stopped halfway
before completing the cross.
It doesn't seem so strange to think
they were killed the same way.
JANG JE-IN'S ROOM
Hey, Je-in.
BACK TO SEARCHING FOR CLUES
You need to tell us something now.
Come on, Je-in.
This is very tricky.
SHAMAN'S ROOM
Hey, come on.
Treat my brother's photo with respect.
Put it right.
I bet the sixth floor is the key.
Don't you all know?
The crime scene always speaks for itself.
That's what we need to find out.
Why and how...
did they know she'd come in here?
There must be something here.
SOMETHING WAS UNDER THE DESK
"Survivor"?
As in Han Survivor?
SOMETHING RELATED
TO THE LATE HAN SURVIVOR?
This must be a clue.
Let's see.
Wait.
What's that?
What's this?
JANG JE-IN'S PHONE
Over here, everyone!
- Jeez, that scared me.
- What is it now?
Over here, everyone!
Up here on the sixth floor!
- Do we have to go?
- Come up now!
Can't you bring it down here?
I can't!
Why'd you call us up here?
Wait. Hold on, everyone!
What's gotten into you?
- While searching this room,
- Yeah?
I found a lead underneath the freezer.
Je-in's phone.
That's crucial evidence.
- Let's see it.
- All right.
MESSAGES
Look.
TEXTS EXCHANGED WITH HAN SURVIVOR
She's been texting Han Survivor
since July 28th.
That was three days ago.
"Mr. Survivor. It's me, Jang Je-in."
"Please call me. I need to speak to you."
Then, on the 29th, "Mr. Survivor,
I really need to talk to you."
On the 31st,
"Mr. Survivor, is everything okay?"
"Please let me know."
Then Han Survivor replied.
"This is Survivor. Something came up,
and I wasn't able to text you back."
"I'll be waiting
at Yeonjidol Hospital at 11 p.m."
But Survivor's dead.
I see what happened.
Je-in left the country quite suddenly,
so she had no idea Han Survivor died.
For five years?
When she came back and reached out to him,
someone pretended to be him
to lure Je-in out and hurt her.
- Isn't it likely?
- Yeah.
But...
I think this other clue
is the conclusive evidence.
CONCLUSIVE EVIDENCE?
Look at this.
"I'll be waiting there
at 10:30 p.m. Survivor."
- At 10:30 p.m. Where's "there"?
-"There."
It must mean this room.
- It's someone who knows about this room.
- Exactly.
But get this.
This note says 10:30 p.m.,
but this text says
to meet him at the hospital at 11 p.m.
There's a high chance
Park Village Head sent the text.
However,
we should note that this other person
made Je-in show up half an hour earlier.
- Yeah.
- Are you responsible
- for the text, Village Head?
- That was me. I admit it.
- Right, this was very likely him.
- You're not lying, are you?
If I were lying, I'd be the killer.
I sent the text,
but I didn't write this note.
So whoever wrote the note
is the real killer.
It's written on paper
from Yeonjidol Hotel.
You're right.
THE KILLER USED A NOTEPAD
FROM YEONJIDOL HOTEL
It's either someone
who knows the hotel manager
or any other staff member
or a guest at the hotel.
KIM HANDSOME IS STAYING AT THE HOTEL
Anyone could've grabbed a piece
from the hotel notepad.
When we asked the hotel manager,
he said Mr. Village Head
dropped by the hotel for an event.
I think he could've grabbed
the piece of paper then.
And also, it's true that he planned
to meet Je-in at 11 p.m. to kill her.
Then where's Han Survivor's cell phone?
If Village Head sent the text,
it must be in his room, right?
Let's try calling. We can call the number.
CALL LOG ON JANG JE-IN'S PHONE
CALLS
HAN SURVIVOR
Let's look for the phone.
We should hear it ring.
This way.
That's Han Survivor's phone.
RINGING FROM THE MOUNTAIN AREA
What's that?
I think we should take this too.
What is it?
Han Survivor's phone!
Where is it coming from?
Where?
Gosh, I'm so scared.
- Why was the phone buried here?
- Found it!
It's Han Survivor's phone.
What is it?
But why is Han Survivor's phone...
Check for voicemails.
There are voicemails.
2 NEW VOICEMAILS FROM DIRECTOR JANG JE-IN
Wait! There are voicemails.
- What?
- Turn up the volume.
- From Je-in?
Je-in left voicemails.
- Is this it?
- Play the first one.
Mr. Survivor,
I'm planning on holding a press conference
to present my research papers in Korea.
I see.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity
for me.
Remember the gang member you mentioned
who's still out there?
I know who he is.
I want to present it as part of
my groundbreaking research results,
but I need your permission first.
But I can't get in touch with you,
and I'm running out of time.
The doctor-patient confidentiality
can be overridden
if the disclosure of information
greatly benefits the public,
so I'm holding the press conference
tomorrow as planned
and sharing this
with the press and the police.
If you get this message,
please call me back.
Mr. Survivor,
I've been waiting to hear from you.
Thanks for reaching out.
I see you didn't specify where to meet.
I'll see you at that place
in the hospital later at 11 p.m.
Where the heck
is "that place in the hospital"?
All right.
So Je-in didn't know
that Han Survivor was dead at this point.
Seems so.
That's why she planned to present him
as a successful case
- at her press conference.
- That's right.
But then...
She said she found the gang member
the police couldn't find.
You know, that...
That's exactly why...
- Hear me out. It won't take long.
- Oh my gosh.
- Jeez, you scared me.
- I'll tell you everything.
I didn't kill her.
Why, you ask?
There was the eve festival
the night before my inauguration,
so I had to be there.
You get it? Now, where did it go?
Hang on, can I just go down first?
- So I got this shovel and this knife...
- Darn it.
- Okay, okay.
- All right.
- Please don't kill us.
- I didn't have much time,
and since we agreed to meet at 11 p.m.,
I dug a hole first, okay?
So I could kill her, bury the body,
and then return to the event.
Kill whom?
- Jang Je-in.
- Okay.
She said she'd report me,
and I heard everything.
So you planned to kill her
- I did.
- and left to meet her at 11.
But then the landslide happened.
LANDSLIDE OCCURRED ON YEONJIDOL MOUNTAIN
You saw all this stuff buried here.
These were all buried here just today.
- Right.
- You mean the tools?
Look at this.
Does it look like this knife
has been buried for five or six years?
- It doesn't!
- Okay! We get it!
Why are you pointing it at me?
What I'm saying is...
Okay, okay, we get it.
- I didn't do it!
- All right.
- Okay.
- You're free to go.
Here's where I stand.
I happened to have killed a few people,
- but I didn't kill Jang Je-in.
- All right.
Well, in that case,
- can I ask you a question?
- Sure.
When you messaged Je-in
to lure her to meet you at 11 p.m.,
- you wrote you'd wait at the hospital.
- Yeah.
Then, Je-in asked you to come
to "that place in the hospital."
I'll see you at that place...
"THAT PLACE" = SECRET OPERATING ROOM
But you didn't know
about "that place," right?
Honestly, no.
I'm not Han Survivor,
so I assumed
that she meant the director's office.
I had no idea about the sixth floor.
- So you just supplied the people.
- I swear...
- You didn't know about the room?
- I just sent her the homeless.
I had no idea what she did with them
or that the sixth floor even existed.
We're never going to
solve the case at this rate.
We'll never find the truth this way.
- Detective, I have a question too.
- Shoot.
Why did you keep so many of these
in your drawers, Shaman?
- These?
- Yeah.
FOUND IN SHAMAN'S SHRINE
- Why are there so many garbage bags here?
- Hang on.
Remember the one up there?
One of these bags
was on the operating room's floor,
where you don't need these at all.
A BLACK PLASTIC BAG ON THE SIXTH FLOOR?
IS IT PARK SHAMAN'S?
Here's my guess.
She would've brought it there
to carry back her brother's organs
on the off chance she found them.
In a plastic bag?
- So people wouldn't see them.
- You'd need something to put them in.
Why would I put the organs
in a plastic bag, of all things?
Where else would you put them in?
Some sort of sacred container,
don't you think?
They're his organs.
Just tell him he's right!
Okay, fine. You're right.
I suppose I did what you said.
- It's just that
- Yes?
I saw that one suspicious plastic bag
on the sixth floor.
Why was it there? That kept nagging at me.
WHY WAS THERE A PLASTIC BAG
IN THE SECRET OPERATING ROOM?
I want to know why.
THERE MUST BE A REASON
By the way, Ms. Park Shaman,
how did you say your brother died?
His body was discovered on the mountain.
But what state was his body in?
Someone had removed all his organs.
- All his organs were removed.
- Yeah.
Now, look here.
Here, and here too.
- There are these suture marks.
- I see them.
How old is that one?
- Her chest--
- Isn't this a surgery scar?
She had thoracic surgery.
- I saw the results of her physical exam.
- What surgery was it?
- Her echocardiogram numbers were very low.
- Her heart...
Did we look at this?
A LITTLE EARLIER
"VIP Physical Exam."
JANG JE-IN'S PHYSICAL EXAM RESULTS
Why are her echocardiogram numbers so low?
- Over here!
- Oh my gosh!
Come here, hurry.
One, two, three.
Oh shit.
THE SHOCKING REVEAL
MADE HER FORGET THE CLUE
Look. It says 34%.
The normal range is from 50 to 70.
Look, it says, "echocardiogram."
The normal range is from 50 to 70,
but hers was 34% in 2011.
But in 2012, it suddenly dropped to 12%.
- Much lower than normal.
- She got worse.
She did. But guess what?
- The next year, it shot up to 63%
- She improved.
It reached the normal range,
out of the blue, in 2013.
- She must've gotten a heart transplant.
- In 2013...
Oh no!
What happened to your brother again?
Oh, please don't.
I think I know the killer.
I can tell you what happened.
- How?
- Go ahead.
- Now?
- Yeah.
We're not going to
find anything new here, are we?
CLOSING IN ON THE CULPRIT?
WHAT IS THE TRUTH
JANG DETECTIVE UNCOVERED?
I think I've gotten close to the truth.
Okay.
Park Shaman,
let's go over your story again.
You really are a shaman, correct?
I am.
You perform rites
and believe in the gods you serve.
Yes. That's why I went so far
as to mummify my brother.
Okay, then.
What's this now?
GO HIGH SHAMAN'S SECRET BOOK OF RITES
CHAPTER 4. PURIFICATION RITES
There's a rite
called the purification rite.
...IF ONE'S BODY IS DESECRATED,
THEIR SOUL WANDERS IN THE AFTERLIFE...
It's to send a soul to the afterlife.
Sending a soul to the afterlife.
Now, there's a particular order
to how this rite is performed.
An Doctor, please read it out loud.
Start with step one.
"First, perform a sacrificial rite
prior to this rite."
"This is to expel the evil spirit
from where the soul died
and to seize the body and soul
of those who stole the dead's body."
"Contain the evil spirit
in an animal carcass
and expel it with a curse."
Okay.
She performed a rite over there
before the murder.
9:20 P.M.
RITE FOR VILLAGE'S WELL-BEING
IN FRONT OF HOSPITAL
- And an animal was sacrificed.
- The pig.
- Next.
- But I didn't plan that rite.
Stop! Allow me.
"Second, begin the purification rite."
"Place the hanji doll
made in the person's likeness
and the deceased's belongings
in the spirit container,
then offer a prayer
to summon the soul of the deceased."
Here, the hanji doll, or paper doll,
in the deceased's likeness.
She put it in the earthenware pot.
PAPER DOLL AND HER BROTHER'S BELONGINGS
KEPT IN THE POT
Okay? She put these in the pot.
-"Third."
- Yes, next.
"Circle the body
while carrying the spirit container,
and offer another heartfelt prayer."
"Now that you've summoned their soul,
collect the parts of the desecrated body
- and unite them."
- She had to collect the body parts!
She told us all of his organs were gone.
So she had to find them.
She had to collect
her dead brother's organs
and bring them all back.
Man, I'm getting goosebumps.
And now, the last step.
"Only then can the deceased ascend to
paradise and not become an evil spirit."
She's trying to
send her brother to the afterlife
because she believes that his soul
is still wandering the earth.
- Can I say my piece now?
- Okay.
This isn't anything special.
It's a common cleansing rite.
That rite is just as common.
All shamans do it. I didn't go out
of my way for my brother or anything.
Just because you found this today
doesn't mean I started it today.
I've been preparing for this rite
ever since I found my brother's body
all those years ago.
We're talking about my brother's soul.
I'm a shaman. This is what I do.
I can't let his soul wander
while I'm helping other souls find peace.
But I would've had to find his organs
to truly complete this rite.
But I haven't.
She doesn't have his heart right now,
but when you apply
the order of that rite from the book
to the crime scene
currently laid out before us,
it fits all too perfectly.
She finally managed to find
her brother's remains on the mountain,
but his heart was missing.
Then, she probably figured out
that Je-in had it transplanted into her.
It's a possibility.
That's why she couldn't bury him
and just left him like that.
But then she heard
that Je-in was coming back.
Keep in mind, she has to send her
brother's wandering soul to the afterlife.
Then, by the logic of that rite,
she would have to recover
what he had lost.
- By that logic, you're right.
- Just think about it, you know.
But I couldn't have known for sure
that Je-in had his heart
because I had no idea
she had heart surgery.
But you could've known
that she had a weak heart.
- Well, that's...
- You said
she had to get treatment after your prank
- in high school.
- She just came back after passing out.
- The report mentioned Je-in's heart.
- It did mention a heart attack.
But I thought she just fainted from shock,
not from a real heart attack.
I never took it that seriously.
I had no professional knowledge
to be able to figure out
that she had a congenital heart disease
just because she almost
had a heart attack.
The more plausible her excuses are,
the more suspicious she seems.
But I'm telling the truth here.
Hey.
What about this, then?
"Memorial tablet of the dead, Brother."
MEMORIAL TABLET
FOUND ON HER BROTHER'S REMAINS
"Memorial tablet."
I just can't seem to
suspect Park Shaman even if I want to.
We've already deduced
that someone intercepted
Je-in's meeting
with Park Village head at 11.
But Park Shaman had no way of knowing
the content of Mr. Village Head's text.
And there's no evidence
to prove that she did.
How could she intercept a meeting
only the two of them knew about?
- I don't think that's possible.
- You do make a very valid point.
Could any one of us have known about
Park Village Head's text?
I'm not sure, but I don't think so.
- Right?
- Yeah.
There were voicemails to Han Survivor.
In his voicemail box?
IN HAN SURVIVOR'S VOICEMAIL BOX
I'll see you at that place
in the hospital later at 11 p.m.
JANG JE-IN'S REPLY
For example,
if she sent that voicemail
while she was at the hotel...
30 MINUTES AGO
- Can I help you?
- Are you aware of Ms. Jang's murder?
I didn't have enough time
to properly look at it,
but someone could've checked
Yeonjidol Hotel's guest list
and found her room number
and other details.
After that,
they could've gone to her room
or approached her
and overheard something.
Or they could've bugged her room.
- Mr. Village Head...
- Yeah?
He knew Je-in was staying in Room 305.
- You're right.
- How?
- The reporter.
- The reporter told him.
- Yeah.
-"I heard she was staying in Room 305."
Then he could've left this note
in Room 305.
Right, and when I asked
the hotel manager about him earlier,
he said Mr. Village Head
came by the hotel.
- With the governor.
- Yeah.
What was held at 11 p.m.?
There was a party,
and the closing ceremony was at 11:50 p.m.
- Were you at the party, Mr. Village Head?
- No, he wasn't.
- He said he kept stepping out.
- He was gone until 11:30 p.m.
The youth association leader
was looking for him,
and he replied, "I'm almost there."
Wait, but this is...
Mr. Village Head was supposed
to say a few words at the end, right?
He got a text confirming that the schedule
was moved up to 11:30 p.m.
- It was moved up to 11:30 p.m.?
- It was.
Let's say he met Je-in at 11 p.m.
- He'd be late.
- He wouldn't have made it back in time.
But he received that text
at 10:03 p.m., right?
If he had read it right away,
- he could've gone up to leave the note.
- And change the time.
If that note was left in front of
or stuck on the door of her hotel room,
Mr. Village Head is the one
most likely to have done it.
He knew her room number
and his whereabouts that day
gave him access to the hotel notepad.
Me?
- Suppose someone came here.
- Okay.
By "someone," I mean this guy.
If he had asked
where his cousin was staying,
surely the manager would've told him.
Think about it.
Jang Cousin received that text.
"Family? Please." That one.
What's more,
he found three clues in a row at the end.
Two upstairs
- and Survivor's phone.
- Right.
I think that settles it.
In addition to all that,
he started to suspect me.
I don't suspect you.
So that's where I... All right, then.
- I suspect someone else.
- If you say so.
I've never met a character
like Mr. Park Village Head.
HIS UNORTHODOX APPROACH CONFUSES HER
- I can't read him.
- I wouldn't kill someone that way.
I do have a bit of a gambler's streak.
I believe if someone falsely accuses me,
they have some skeletons in their closet.
- I'm thinking in terms of this whole game.
- Okay.
Now, we'll have a three-minute session
for a final sweep.
I hope you all find the real culprit.
We haven't been
this split in opinion for a while.
We must've missed some clues.
Last chance.
Will we find some more clues?
Je-in!
What could you have possibly done
to deserve such a gruesome death?
CAST YOUR VOTE BASED ON THE CLUES
You know...
this text is too suspicious.
Someone had to leave her that note
to lure her to the hospital.
Let's think about why they left the note.
It was to move up the meeting.
And why was that?
Because the closing ceremony was moved up.
Mr. Village Head
was in too much of a hurry,
which is why he had to leave a note
to meet her 30 minutes earlier.
Then, how did he know
about the sixth floor?
Because he knew
about her secret experiments.
She was supplying him with free labor.
He said there was nothing more to it,
but there's no proof to back it up.
Also...
The reporter sent Mr. Village Head a text
regarding which hotel
and what room Je-in is staying in.
But that wasn't all
that the reporter told him.
They told Mr. Village Head
about her press conference.
What was that press conference about?
Han Survivor.
Who killed Han Survivor?
Park Village Head.
Je-in said she found out the identity
of the gang member
who evaded police,
and Park Village Head would've known
he was the one she was talking about.
I'm holding the press conference
tomorrow as planned
and sharing this
with the press and the police.
That day was the day of his inauguration.
He was about to lose
everything he had worked so hard for.
That might've driven him
to move up the meeting
and kill her right then and there.
To keep his true identity
as Park Enforcer a secret,
he killed Jang Je-in.
AN DOCTOR AND PARK SHAMAN
CHOSE PARK VILLAGE HEAD
PARK VILLAGE HEAD
PARK VILLAGE HEAD: 2, PARK SHAMAN: 1
At first,
I thought An Doctor was the killer.
But nothing's scarier
than a vengeful family member.
His father was the eldest,
but the second son got the inheritance.
So he wouldn't have given up
on the hospital building
because there was gold buried there
that only he knew about.
He probably constantly searched the place,
which makes him the most likely person
to have discovered the sixth floor.
My gambler's heart
tells me to pick Jang Cousin.
PARK VILLAGE HEAD CHOSE JANG COUSIN
JANG COUSIN
"The crime scene
always speaks for itself."
An Doctor was caught on camera
during that live stream,
and the gown and cap
she was wearing in the video
were all identical
to the ones we found on the sixth floor.
Also, you can only get to the sixth floor
by taking the elevator.
But you need diesel fuel
to get the elevator running,
and An Doctor did buy 10,000 won's worth.
It was you.
JANG COUSIN CHOSE AN DOCTOR
JANG DETECTIVE'S FINAL 3 MINUTES
MEMORIAL TABLET OF THE DEAD, BROTHER
Okay.
There's no doubt.
JANG DETECTIVE CHOSE PARK SHAMAN
PARK VILLAGE HEAD: 2, PARK SHAMAN: 2
In any case,
you can't always find all the clues
and complete the puzzle perfectly.
You have to make a choice
after weighing the possibilities.
The killer slashed both her shoulders.
Seems like they wanted to
dismember her completely.
BRUTALIZED TO AN UNUSUAL DEGREE
He's killed a lot of people before
and in various ways.
So if anyone can carry out
a murder this brutal,
it's Park Village Head.
WORK OF A FORMER GANG MEMBER?
But there is another possibility.
Maybe Park Shaman
wanted to take out Je-in's heart,
but her time was suddenly cut short.
That could've been why
she was forced to run away
without actually accomplishing her goal.
That could be a possibility.
This case...
was particularly tough.
The one who killed my Je-in...
is you.
FINAL VOTE COMPLETE
The very first episode
of the deduction game, Crime Scene Zero.
- I recognize her voice. So it's all live.
- You bet it is.
The results of the nail-biting
deduction game to find the culprit
of the murder
in the abandoned hospital are in.
Let's see who received the most votes
as the real culprit.
We will now
announce the results.
I'm nervous.
First, we will announce who was excluded
from the final list of suspects.
With zero votes...
Kim Handsome, you are excluded
from the final lineup.
Wait, no one picked me?
No one likes me?
- It was because you're out of your mind.
- Pull yourself together.
- You're off the list for sure.
- Please like me.
- Next.
- There's more?
With one vote...
An Doctor...
and Jang Cousin,
you are also excluded
from the final lineup.
- Did you vote for each other?
- No.
- Did you?
- I didn't.
And so, Park Village Head and Park Shaman
were identified as suspects.
Which one of you messed up this time?
Why are there two final suspects?
- So this is how it went.
- This is wrong.
Will the two final suspects
please step forward?
The ultimate deduction game,
Crime Scene Zero.
The results of the final vote
of the murder in the abandoned hospital.
The player who was ultimately identified
as the culprit is...
Man, this one was tough.
In a three to two split,
the player with three votes is...
Park Shaman!
- What?
Wow, this is...
KIM HANDSOME CHOSE PARK SHAMAN
- Park Shaman?
- Me?
Really?
- Looks like it's her.
- Park Shaman?
Park Shaman, you've been identified
as the final suspect.
Please enter the jail.
Mole-rye!
-"Mole-rye."
- Hey, Mole-sun.
What did you do?
It wasn't me.
- Mole-rye.
- How could this happen?
Thank goodness we captured Mole-sun,
my Je-in's killer.
The players who voted for Park Shaman,
Jang Detective
and Kim Handsome,
please step forward.
- He gets two votes?
- That brat.
- He cast one vote earlier.
- Yeah, halfway through.
This is because of your first vote,
Detective.
Wait.
Two people voted for Park Village Head?
Wow, that was close.
We could've been in real trouble.
What do you mean, "real trouble"?
If Park Shaman is the real culprit,
Jang Detective and Kim Handsome
will each win two million won.
If Park Shaman is not the culprit,
the real killer will claim the prize money
of all other players,
a total of ten million won.
- The real killer gets it?
- A whopping ten million won?
- Not those who voted for the culprit?
- Ten million?
Park Shaman has been voted as the culprit
in the murder in the abandoned hospital.
Let me load up on a few tears of joy.
If we're wrong about this,
hand me that whole bottle of eye drops.
Is she really the culprit
who killed Jang Je-in?
Ms. Park Shaman.
"Are you..."
Are you...
Jang Je-in's killer?
I wonder.
- Oh, come on!
- Jeez!
I wonder.
HEARTS RACING
Since when did you toy with us?
We have to watch our blood pressure
and heart health. Please don't do that.
I have to put more drops in now.
Ms. Park Shaman.
Are you...
I'm suddenly a bit worried.
- Why? Don't be.
- I have no idea.
...Jang Je-in's killer?
Je-in...
Yes, she is!
SUCCESSFULLY APPREHENDED THE CULPRIT
I knew it!
- I told you it wasn't me!
- We caught my Je-in's killer!
I mean, come on.
I kept pushing her as the prime suspect.
- How could you?
- Well, I...
But there was one thing
that was nagging at me.
Only the word "brother"
was written in Korean on the tablet,
and that really bothered me.
Here it is.
DURING THE FINAL EXAMINATION OF THE SCENE
Oh man, I was an idiot.
Why did I
just let this slide?
I thought about why
only the word "brother"
was written in Korean.
And when it comes to the word
for "the dead,"
normally, the character used for it
is the one that means "person," not "son."
And in this particular case,
she should actually use
the character for "younger male sibling."
So when I thought about why she didn't,
it just hit me.
He was her son.
You only write the character "son"
to mean the deceased
- when the deceased is your son.
- What?
How would they know any of that?
So, "Brother" is her son's name in Korean.
The moment I figured that out--
He was your son?
Yes.
- Why would you name your son "Brother"?
- I should boil you alive!
Who names their son "Brother"?
I named him "Brother"
because I raised him like one.
All the clues were in the memorial tablet.
We'll now announce
the key piece of evidence you missed.
I'm dying to know.
How did she know about the sixth floor?
Take a look under the headboard
of the bed in Jang Je-in's hotel room.
Hey, who searched this room?
What's this?
It's a bug. Damn it.
- This?
- A bug?
- How do you turn this on?
- So that's how.
She must've been listening in
when Je-in left that message.
She bugged her room!
That was why she moved up the meeting.
Wow, I had no idea.
- Did you kill her wearing that gown?
- Yeah.
Darn it!
Why the heck would you wear that?
- Why can't I?
- Is that what you're mad about?
Unbelievable.
Did that black plastic bag
have nothing to do with it?
No, I brought it with me
to put the heart in there.
I was right about the plastic bag.
She said she meant to carry
the heart in that bag.
No one believed me.
That's rich. You voted for me!
Why'd you have to
go find three clues at the end?
Actually, I was worried
you'd find the plastic bag,
so I slid it away with my foot to hide it.
But he still somehow found it.
Mr. Village Head, you found
a key piece of evidence.
- Great job.
- Good work.
Your voice was so strong.
You gave a great performance.
THE FULL STORY BEHIND
THE MURDER IN THE ABANDONED HOSPITAL
Park Shaman grew up extremely poor
in Yeonjidol Village
and was bullied
throughout her school years
by Jang Je-in, the only daughter
of an influential local resident.
In the winter
of her final year in high school,
she couldn't take the bullying any longer
and attempted a minor revenge on Je-in
by slipping a dead mouse in her backpack.
But Je-in collapsed in shock,
clutching at her heart,
and was taken to the emergency room.
It was revealed that Je-in
had a congenital heart disease,
and Shaman was expelled
right before graduation
for endangering the life
of an influential local's daughter.
She then moved to Seoul for work
and started dating Gu Male Doc,
a medical student at E-Ryu University.
Just as she was becoming happy,
she was suddenly possessed by a god
and also found herself
unexpectedly pregnant.
Gu Male Doc heartlessly left her
after throwing her some money
for an abortion.
In fact,
Gu Male Doc had fallen for Jang Je-in,
a fellow medical student,
and left Shaman for her.
She gave birth as a single mother,
but her son was born blind.
To protect him from the inherited fate
of becoming a shaman,
she registered him
not as her son but as her brother
and sent him to be raised by her mother,
who lived alone.
The only hope Shaman had
was to raise 500 million won
for the surgery
that could restore her son's eyesight.
But one day,
her mother passed away.
Shaman then returned to Yeonjidol Village
to take care of her son.
However,
by some cruel twist of fate,
Je-in also returned to Yeonjidol Village
that same year
and opened a psychiatric hospital.
As revenge on Je-in,
Shaman spread false rumors
among the families of the patients
that the hospital
was haunted by evil spirits
and charged them exorbitant prices
for rites and talismans,
finally raising the 500 million won
for her son's surgery.
But once Je-in found out,
she reported Shaman to the police,
leaving her to be taken into custody.
When she was finally released
after ten days,
she rushed back home,
only to find that her son had disappeared.
She searched the whole village,
but he had vanished without a trace.
However,
Yeonjidol Psychiatric Hospital closed down
while Shaman was in custody,
and Je-in also disappeared.
This triggered her intuition
as a mother and shaman,
and she frantically began
searching the hospital.
In the elevator,
she discovered a hidden button.
And upon pressing it,
she arrived on the sixth floor,
which was hidden from the outside.
There, she found a secret operating room
where Je-in
illegally practiced frontal lobotomies.
And inside a freezer tucked in the corner
was the body of her son
she'd been desperately searching for,
abandoned with his heart ripped out.
At that moment,
Shaman remembered
Je-in's congenital heart disease
and realized that Je-in had locked her up
and taken her son's heart
while she was in custody.
COMPLAINT
Since her son was mutilated
and died away from home,
he was fated to become an evil spirit.
To prevent this,
Shaman had to recover his heart from Je-in
and perform a purification rite.
Shaman mummified her son's body and put it
inside the Buddha statue at her shrine
to serve and honor it,
and waited for Je-in's return.
Five years later,
to prepare for the rite
to be performed at the eve festival,
Shaman dropped by Yeonjidol Hotel
and heard the news that Je-in was back
and staying at the hotel.
The next day,
while Chong Manager was distracted,
she secretly checked the guest list
and stole the master key
to install a bug in Je-in's room.
She discovered that Je-in agreed to meet
with someone named Han Survivor
at 11 p.m. that night at "that place"
in Yeonjidol Psychiatric Hospital.
Shaman recalled Han Survivor's name,
which she had seen years ago
in the secret operating room.
That meant
the two were going to meet
in the secret room on the sixth floor.
Thinking this was the perfect opportunity
for her to take her son's heart
back from Je-in,
Shaman left a note
pretending to be Han Survivor
to get her to show up 30 minutes earlier.
The first step in the purification rite
to appease her son's restless soul
was to perform a sacrificial rite.
She moved the location from the hotel
to the front of the hospital,
and instead of praying
for the village's peace,
she cast a curse on Je-in.
She then returned home to place
the paper doll in her son's likeness
and his belongings
in the spirit container.
Then, Shaman grabbed
a plastic bag for the heart
and a container full of diesel
and headed to the hospital.
She filled
the emergency generator with diesel,
got the elevator running,
and hid in the secret operating room
on the sixth floor.
At 10:30 p.m.,
when Je-in arrived at the operating room,
Shaman rendered her unconscious
by striking her in the head with a hammer.
She was about to open Je-in's chest
with an electric saw to take her heart
when Je-in woke up screaming.
A fierce struggle ensued,
with Je-in trying to escape
and Shaman trying to catch her.
Je-in attempted to escape
through the window onto the ledge.
Deciding to take the heart
after making her fall off the ledge,
Shaman slashed Je-in's left wrist,
as she held onto the hospital sign,
with the electric saw.
Unable to hold on any longer,
Je-in eventually fell
and got caught in the tangled power wires
on the outer wall of the hospital.
Unable to extract Je-in's heart
or retrieve and discard her body,
Shaman was at a loss.
But the clock neared 11 p.m.,
the time Han Survivor
was expected to come.
So she had no choice
but to return to her shrine.
She vowed to extract her son's heart
once Je-in's body
was recovered and buried
and continued praying.
Hey.
Yes?
JOO DAUGHTER-IN-LAW
JANG YOUNGEST'S ROOM
- You...
- Did you knock out this wall?
- Did you seduce my son?
- Oh my goodness!
Hang on a second.
Please let go of me first.
- Let go of me.
- No, I won't. I'll let go once you talk.
- Let go and I'll talk.
- Talk and I'll let go.
- You want this to go on forever?
- Let go.
- I don't exactly need an answer.
I don't feel like talking either.
- Then I'll keep holding on.
- Okay, then. Shall we?
- Let's go.
- Fine by me.
Subtitle translation by: Yenny Kang